

Contact

- +33 761 935 596
- paulviudes17@gmail.com
- 2b Traverse du Mas de Gidde, 13500 Martigues, France

Education

2022 - 2023

Specialised Masters in Interactive and Game Experience Design Gobelins

2019 - 2022

Engineering degree in Computer science and Multimedia Enjimin- Cnam

2017- 2019

Techical degree in computer science specialized in digital imaging Aix-Marseille University

2017- 2019

Third cycle of music theory and percussion

Martigues Music Conservatory

Skills

- Unity
- C++ (OpenGL)
- Unreal EngineJira / Notion
- Godot
- Reaper / Fmod

Languages

English: TOIEC 840

French : Native

Spanish: C1

PAUL Viudes

Game Developer

About me

Hello, my name is Paul Viudes. After six years of higher education in computer science and video games, including four years of work-study, I am seeking a job in the video game industry to progress both creatively and technically.

Experience

Game Developer apprenticeship

2022 - 2023 Universcience

For the renovation of the "palais de la découverte" science museum, I co-designed 23 experiments. My other mission was research and development, with the creation of prototypes.

XR engineer apprenticeship

2019 - 2022 CEA (Alternative Energies and Atomic Energy Commission)

During this apprenticeship, I have developed on many technologies like AR, VR, and haptics. The objective was to help in the qualification and design of a nuclear fusion machine.

Riri & Coco

2022

Global Game Jam Var

With 6 friends, we created a game called Riri & Coco during the Global Game Jam 2022. It's a small collaborative game where players embody two characters from children's stories, and we must solve various puzzles as quickly as possible using each character's abilities. This game is still in development alongside our respective studies.

Hobbies

- **Create Video Games**
- Play Guitar/Percussion/Bass
- Watch genre films
- Climbing